CARLOS ABDU

FREELANCE ARTIST, DESIGNER, WRITER, EDITOR & NOW, CODER.

> ABOUT ME

Perseverance. Creativity. Integrity. These are the tenants that motivates this hard-working creative, whether through paint, prose or code. Full Stack Web Development proficient in an array of different languages, specializing in Front-End Development. Exceptional Cartoonist and Conceptual Designer that loves both digital and traditional artistic mediums. Has skills in writing, editing, media editing, photography, data organization, streaming, podcasting, interpretive dancing, kazoo playing & ranting with a minor doctorate in general clowning around.

> SKILLS

TECH TOOLS

JavaScript

JQuery

CSS

HTML

GitHub

WordPress.

Sublime

Atom

React Ruby

nuby

Ruby on Rails

Postico

HTML Canvas

DIGITAL VIDEO AND MEDIA

Adobe Creative Cloud Premiere Pro Adobe Creative Cloud After Effects Adobe Creative Cloud Audition Adobe Creative Cloud Dreamweaver Acrobat Pro DC OBS Studio

DIGITAL ILLUSTRATION

Adobe Creative Cloud Photoshop Adobe Creative Cloud Illustrator Clip Paint Studio Corel Painter XI TV PaintPro 10

> ACTIVITIES

Mighty Mutts and Ollie's Place · Part-Time Volunteer New York, NY Sept. 2017 to Current

Assisting in presenting and aiding foster dogs being shown to potential adopters.

> CONTACT

 □ carabdu@gmail.com

carbonmade.com/carloscontrarian

347-306-2644

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/carlos-abdu-58754751/

> EXPERIENCE

N & Y Elder Care, Inc. (Now Corkus Home Care LLC.)
Patient Care Taker · Brooklyn, NY May 2018 to Aug. 2018

- Attending to the client's needs and providing pleasant company.
 Engaged in light cleaning and organizational duties on the client's request.
- Responsible for maintaining the schedule of the client's medical appointments and attending the appointments on time to provide added security and translation.

ARM Management

Administrative Assistant · Sept. 2017 to Jan. 2018, Sept. 2017 to Brooklyn, NY Jan. 2018

- Data entry and backing up important files to digital conversion.
- Clerical work, receiving phone calls, doing minor investigations on the conditions of various properties.
- Listing properties for rent/sale on various internet platforms.

Greenpeace NYC

Canvasser New York, NY

June 2017 to Aug. 2017

- This role involved exceptional people skills and salesmanship, to convince interested parties in supporting environmental issues.
- Assisted in various campaigns, protests, and events in the New York area that rallied against terrible
- Went door to door to raise awareness against arctic drilling, to check on the status of previous members and recruit new members.

Sign N Signs

Junior Graphic Designer · Brooklyn, NY

May 2015 to Mar. 2016

Offered illustration and digital design skills to various local customers in order to provide various type of advertisements for their businesses, ranging from awnings to brochures.

> EDUCATION

General Assembly

Oct. 2018 to Jan. 2019

Certificate of Completion Web Development 2019

The second phase of the Per Scholas web development immersive

Per Scholas - CodeBridge

Aug. 2018 to Oct. 2018

Graduated the Per Scholas portion of the intensive bootcamp - The first phase of The CodeBridge WDI program

Brooklyn College B.S., Fine Art 2010 Sept. 2006 to Sept. 2010

Took an extra year and upgraded from Art to Fine Art to take an extra classes

New York City College of Technology Sept. 2002 to Sept. 2006 Associates Art and Advertising Design 2006